{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Solid Surface Countertop Repair Companies","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40204/":{"taskOID":40204,"originalTaskOID":40204,"setID":511,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":265,"questionDisplayText":"Problem Description","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select the best description(s) of the countertop problem you need repaired.  (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5500,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Scratch","answerDisplayText":"Scratch","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1687,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Crack","answerDisplayText":"Crack","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1867,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Delaminating","answerDisplayText":"Delaminating","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1193,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Burn","answerDisplayText":"Burn","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1148,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Bubble","answerDisplayText":"Bubble","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1382,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Chip","answerDisplayText":"Chip","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1940,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Discoloration","answerDisplayText":"Discoloration","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":13,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":265,"questionDisplayText":"Problem Description","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select the best description(s) of the countertop problem you need repaired.  (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5500,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Scratch","answerDisplayText":"Scratch","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1687,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Crack","answerDisplayText":"Crack","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1867,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Delaminating","answerDisplayText":"Delaminating","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1193,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Burn","answerDisplayText":"Burn","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1148,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Bubble","answerDisplayText":"Bubble","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1382,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Chip","answerDisplayText":"Chip","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1940,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Discoloration","answerDisplayText":"Discoloration","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5500,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Scratch","answerDisplayText":"Scratch","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1687,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Crack","answerDisplayText":"Crack","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1867,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Delaminating","answerDisplayText":"Delaminating","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1193,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Burn","answerDisplayText":"Burn","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1148,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Bubble","answerDisplayText":"Bubble","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1382,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Chip","answerDisplayText":"Chip","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1940,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Discoloration","answerDisplayText":"Discoloration","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":13,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/40204/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40204,"taskName":"Solid Surface Countertops - Repair (Concrete, Stainless Steel, etc)","taskDescription":"Repair Solid Surface Countertops","xmTaskDescriptor":"Solid Surface Countertop Repair Companies","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":52,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"corian marble formica counter tops","textMessagingName":"Repr Solid Counters","rolloverLongDesc":"Often called Corian, which is one popular brand. Comes in many colors \u0026 can have contrasting colors inlaid in the edges. The edges can be custom molded or cut in a wide variety of shapes. The plastic material on the surface runs all the way through the counter. Cracks, gouges \u0026 burn marks can be repaired.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes vanities, desktops \u0026 countertops.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Repair Solid Surface Countertops.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Solid Surface Countertop Repair \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Fix Hard Surface Counters","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":8,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Solid Surface Countertop Repair","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Solid Surface (Concrete, Stainless Steel, etc) Countertops- Repair","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Solid Surface Countertop Project","urlName":"Solid-Surface-Corian-Concrete-Stainless-Steel-etc-Countertops-Repair","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Solid Surface Countertop Repair Pros - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Corian, Formica, Steel","searchKeywords":"corian,marble,formica,counter,tops,countertop,top,granite","emcCategoryOid":-12016,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":511,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}